{
    "subject": "resource/Charles_H._Adams_(New_York_politician)",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Coxsackie,_New_York",
    "human_readable": "Charles H. Adams was born in Coxsackie, New York.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8963874578475952,
            "question": "Were there any notable industries or businesses in Coxsackie when Charles H. Adams was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8719552755355835,
            "question": "Where was Charles H. Adams born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5712856650352478,
            "question": "What kind of information can you find about people born in Coxsackie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49221688508987427,
            "question": "What state is Coxsackie located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48126915097236633,
            "question": "What might have been important events happening in Coxsackie during the time of his birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3913857936859131,
            "question": "Do you know any historical figures from Coxsackie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38973239064216614,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Charles H. Adams?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2693808972835541,
            "question": "Are there any records or archives related to Charles H. Adams and his family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0819779559969902,
            "question": "How might his birthplace have influenced his life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.0359322614967823,
            "question": "Is there anything else known about his early life?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Charles H. Adams was born in Coxsackie, New York.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3317_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How might his birthplace have influenced his life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3317_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any records or archives related to Charles H. Adams and his family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3317_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Charles H. Adams?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3317_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3317_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3317_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3317_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3317_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3317_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3317_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3317_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3317_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3317_95.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3317_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After evaluating the context information and the query, I get:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n\nExplanation: The query asks if Charles H. Adams was born in Coxsackie, New York, but the documents mention different birthplaces for Charles Henry Adams (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3317/re-ranker-msmarco/74.txt) and no information is provided about Charles H. Adams' birthplace."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents support the statement that Charles H. Adams was born in Coxsackie, New York, as it is explicitly mentioned in multiple documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It contradicts the information provided in excerpt 1, where it explicitly states \"Mr. Charles Henry Adams was born in Coxsackie, Greene County, N. Y.\" However, excerpt 2 states that he was actually born in Coxsackie, New York, but does not specify the county, which could imply that it is different from Greene County mentioned in excerpt 1.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}